<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CoWApp</string>
    //Main
    <string name="menu_log">LOG</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_info">Info</string>
    <string name="menu_test">Test</string>
    <string name="report_infection_button">Report Infection</string>
    <string name="suspicion_button">Suspicion?</string>
    <string name="risk_status_default">___ : ___ risk</string>
    <string name="daysSinceText">You have been helping to contain the coronavirus for __ days.</string>
    //Data Protection
    <string name="accept_button">Accept</string>
    <string name="decline_button">Decline</string>
    <string name="head_data_protection">Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="text_data_protection">You agree that CoWApp is allowed to activate the Bluetooth of your device and send or receive data via it (generated keys with time stamp     and location as well as information about your current infection status). Furthermore you agree that the app may run as a background process     on your mobile device at any time and is allowed to send your generated and collected anonymous keys to the server if there is an existing infection and you push notifications, too. This is the only way the correct function of the     Corona-Warn-App is given.</string>
    //Info
    <string name="head_info">General Information</string>
    <string name="text_info">The CoWApp (Corona Warning App) is an application that anyone can use to further contain the spread of the coronavirus.     With it potential contact with corona-infected people can be determined in everyday life and an infection risk can be calculated. It is and     displayed by the traffic light principle and a risk value of 1 to 100. You will also receive a push notification when a potential health risk     has been identified so you know how to act correctly to protect yourself and those around you.     Under Suspicion? you can receive information on what to do if you suspect an infection.</string>
    //LOG
    <string name="text_log">Notification Log</string>
    <string name="log">This is a notification</string>
    //Push Notification
    <string name="channel_name">NotificationChannel</string>
    <string name="channel_description">This channel is for push notifications to inform about possible health risk</string>
    <string name="ok_button">Okay</string>
    <string name="head_notification">Possible health risk</string>
    <string name="text_notification">A person with whom you were in direct or indirect contact has been infected with the corona virus.     Please let yourself be tested and go into quarantine until you receive a negative test result.</string>
    //Report Infection
    <string name="report_no_button">No</string>
    <string name="report_yes_button">Yes</string>
    <string name="text_report_infection">Do you really want to report yourself infected? (Only with positive PCR test result.)</string>
    //Settings
    <string name="setting_1">Setting 1</string>
    <string name="setting_2">Setting 2</string>
    //Suspicion
    <string name="head_suspicion_info">Suspicion? - What to do?</string>
    <string name="text_suspicion_info">In case of suspicion, please go into quarantine immediately and let yourself be tested.     If the test result is positive, please inform the health department for your region     and stay in quarantine for 14 days. If the test result is negative, you can end the quarantine.     Thank you for your help to dam the further spread of the corona virus.</string>
    //Test Menu
    <string name="head_test_menu">Test menu</string>
    <string name="test_button_1">push notification test</string>
    <string name="test_button_2">key generation test</string>
    <string name="test_button_3">risk level test</string>
    <string name="test_button_4">check infection status test</string>
    <string name="test_button_5">log own keys test</string>
    <string name="test_button_6">delete own keys test</string>
    <string name="reset_button_risklevel">reset risk level</string>
    <string name="test_button_7">Transmitting on/off</string>
    <string name="test_button_8">Scanning on/off</string>
    //Thank You Screen
    <string name="head_thank_you">Thank you for the report!</string>
    <string name="text_thank_you">The app warns your surroundings. Please inform your local health department and immediately go into 14-day quarantine.</string>
</resources>