<resources>
    //General
    <string name="app_name">CoWApp</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    //Data Protection
    <string name="accept_button">Accept</string>
    <string name="decline_button">Decline</string>
    <string name="head_data_protection">Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="text_data_protection">You agree that CoWApp is allowed to activate the Bluetooth of your device and send or receive data via it (generated keys with time stamp and location as well as information about your current infection status). \nPermission to activate your GPS location is also required for this in order to enable Bluetooth transmission with people in your surroundings. \nFurthermore you agree that the app may run as a background process on your mobile device at any time and is allowed to send your generated and collected anonymous keys to the server if there is an existing infection and you push notifications, too. \nThis is the only way the correct function of the Corona-Warn-App is given.</string>
    <string name="decline_info_title">Agreement required </string>
    <string name="decline_info_message">You have to accept the terms of use to use the application. </string>
    <string name="decline_info_ok_button">Okay</string>
    <string name="exit_app">Exit</string>
    //Permission Requesting
    <string name="background_location_access_title">This app needs background location access</string>
    <string name="background_location_access_message">Please grant location access so this app can detect COVID contacts in the background</string>
    <string name="background_location_access_denied_title">Functionality limited</string>
    <string name="background_location_access_denied_message">Since background location access has not been granted, this app will not be able to discover COVID contacts in the background.  Please go to Settings -> Applications -> Permissions and grant background location access to this app</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_enabled_title">Bluetooth not enabled</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_enabled_message">Please enable Bluetooth and restart the application or use "Request Permissions again"</string>
    <string name="ble_available_title">Bluetooth LE not available</string>
    <string name="ble_available_message">This device doesn\'t support Bluetooth-Low-Energy technology. Therefore you won\'t be able to use the app on this device</string>
    <string name="location_access_denied_message">Since location access has not been granted, this app will not be able to discover COVID contacts in the background</string>
    <string name="background_location_denied">Since background location access has not been granted, this app will not be able to discover beacons when in the background</string>
    <string name="request_permission">Request permissions again</string>
    //Main
    <string name="menu_log">LOG</string>
    <string name="menu_info">Info</string>
    <string name="menu_test">Test</string>
    <string name="menu_report_negative">Negative test result</string>
    <string name="report_infection_button">Report Infection</string>
    <string name="report_infection_button_ci">Further Information</string>
    <string name="suspicion_button">Suspicion?</string>
    <string name="suspicion_button_ci">Negative Test Result</string>
    <string name="traffic_light_description">View to show the current risk status via traffic light status.</string>
    <string name="infoRiskCalcButton_description">Click to show the information page about the risk level calculation.</string>
    <string name="check_bluetooth_enabled_title">Please enable Bluetooth</string>
    <string name="check_bluetooth_enabled_message">Your Bluetooth is disabled.\nThe App needs Bluetooth and GPS (Location) to be always turned on to detect Covid contacts.</string>
    <string name="check_gps_enabled_title">Please enable GPS (Location)</string>
    <string name="check_gps_enabled_message">Your GPS (Location) is disabled.\nThe App needs Bluetooth and GPS (Location) to be always turned on to detect Covid contacts.</string>
    //Main risk status
    <string name="risk_status_default">Current risk</string>
    <string name="risk_status_low">Low Risk</string>
    <string name="risk_status_moderate">Moderate Risk</string>
    <string name="risk_status_high">High Risk</string>
    <string name="risk_level">Risk Level: %1$d of 100</string>
    <string name="current_infection">Current Infection</string>
    //Report Infection / negative test result
    <string name="report_no_button">No</string>
    <string name="report_yes_button">Yes</string>
    <string name="head_report_infection">Report Infection</string>
    <string name="head_report_negative">Report Negative Test Result</string>
    <string name="text_report_infection">Do you really want to report yourself infected? \n(Only with positive PCR test result.)</string>
    <string name="text_report_negative">Do you really want to report yourself negative? \n(Only with negative PCR test result.)</string>
    <string name="head_thank_you">Thank you for the report!</string>
    <string name="text_thank_you">The app warns your surroundings. Please inform your local health department and immediately go into 14-day quarantine.</string>
    <string name="head_report_successful">Report successful</string>
    <string name="text_report_successful">You have been successfully reported negative. Thank you!</string>
    //Date and days since use
    <string name="daysSinceText">Since %1$s you are helping for %2$d days to fight the Coronavirus.</string>
    //Info Menu and pages
    <string name="head_info_menu">Further Information</string>
    <string name="head_general_info">General Information</string>
    <string name="text_general_info">The CoWApp (Corona Warning App) is an application that anyone can use to further contain the spread of the coronavirus. \nWith it potential contact with corona-infected people can be determined in everyday life and an infection risk can be calculated. It is displayed by the traffic light principle and a risk value of 1 to 100. \nYou will also receive a push notification when a potential health risk has been identified so you know how to act correctly to protect yourself and those around you. \nUnder Suspicion? you can receive information on what to do if you suspect an infection.</string>
    //Info screen about the risk level
    <string name="head_risklevel_info">Risk Level Information</string>
    <string name="head_risklevel_value_traffic_light_info">Risk Level and Traffic Light Explanation:</string>
    <string name="text_risklevel_value_traffic_light_info">To clarify to the user how high his risk of infection is, the CoW–App provides a risk level value, which is a numerical value between 0 (no risk) and 100 (existing infection).For further clarity and how the user should best behave, the CoWApp divides and simplifies the risk level via the traffic light display. A risk value less than 35 (i.e. 0 – 34) results in a green traffic light color, which signals to the user that an infection is very unlikely and that he can therefore be unconcerned. A value between 35 and 70 results in a yellow traffic light color, which means that an infection is already possible but not very likely.If the risk level is in the lower range, close to 35, an infection is unlikely. In order to relieve the health care system, no measures should be considered that burden the health care system. However, if the risk level is close to the upper limit of 70, measures such as a corona test are recommended, as the possibility of infection is more likely.A risk level above 70 causes the traffic light to turn red, indicating a high probability of infection. Measures such as a corona test, keeping distance from other people and even quarantine are strongly recommended.</string>
    <string name="head_risklevel_calculation_info">Explanation of the Calculation</string>
    <string name="text_risklevel_calculation_info">To understand the calculation the following terms should be clarified first. contact: A so-called contact was determined by the exchange of keys between end devices. Only contacts with users who are already infected or subsequently reported as infected are included in the risk calculation. These contacts are further specified by evaluating them as either direct or indirect contact. Direct contact: means that there has been contact with a person reported as infected. Indirect contact means a contact with a person who is not reported as infected itself, but has had contact with a third person who is reported as infected To calculate the risk level, all direct and indirect contacts as well as the user\'s self-infection report from the last 14 days are taken into account. The duration of the contacts is also included in the calculation.</string>
    //Infection info
    <string name="head_infection_info">Current Infection - How to act?</string>
    <string name="text_infection_info">In the event of an acute infection, you are obliged to go into quarantine immediately and remain in quarantine for 14 days or until you receive a negative PCR test result. \nYou are also obliged to notify your local health department. \nAny roommates should also be tested immediately and you are encouraged to distance yourself from them. \nFurther information at the page of the federal government or the WHO: https://www.bundesregierung.de/breg-de/themen/coronavirus/coronavirus-wissen for German speaking people or https://www.who.int/health-topics/coronavirus#tab=tab_1 for general information.</string>
    //Suspicion
    <string name="head_suspicion_info">Suspicion? - What to do?</string>
    <string name="text_suspicion_info">In case of suspicion, please go into quarantine immediately and let yourself be tested. \nIf the test result is positive, please inform the health department for your region and stay in quarantine for 14 days. \nIf the test result is negative, you can end the quarantine. \nThank you for your help to dam the further spread of the corona virus.</string>
    //LOG
    <string name="text_log">Notification Log</string>
    <string name="log">This is a notification</string>
    //Push Notification
    <string name="channel_name">NotificationChannel</string>
    <string name="channel_description">This channel is for push notifications to inform about possible health risk</string>
    <string name="ok_button">Okay</string>
    <string name="head_notification">Possible health risk</string>
    <string name="text_notification">A person with whom you were in direct or indirect contact has been infected with the corona virus. Please let yourself be tested and go into quarantine until you receive a negative test result.</string>
    <string name="head_directContactPush">Direct contact with an infected person detected</string>
    <string name="text_moreInfoPush">Tap for further information.</string>
    <string name="head_indirectContactPush">Indirect contact with an infected person detected</string>
    <string name="head_noConnectionPush">Currently no connection to the server</string>
    <string name="text_noConnectionPush">Trying to connect again in 5 minutes…</string>
    //BeaconBackgroundService (foreground) Notification
    <string name="foreground_Notificaiton">Protection active</string>
    //Debug Menu
    <string name="actions">Test-Actions</string>
    <string name="logs">Debug-Log-Settings</string>
    <string name="debuglog">Debug-Log</string>
    <string name="debug_settings_headline">What do you want to log?</string>
    <string name="debug_settings_delete">CLEAR DEBUG LOG</string>
    <string name="debug_settings_update">UPDATE SETTINGS</string>
    <string name="debug_settings_alarm">when the alarm rings</string>
    <string name="debug_settings_alarmset">when the alarm is set</string>
    <string name="debug_settings_keytransmit">when a key is transmitted</string>
    <string name="debug_settings_keysafe">when a key is saved</string>
    <string name="key_was_saved">Key was saved:</string>
    <string name="received_a_key">Received a Key: </string>
    <string name="alarm_ringed">Alarm ring.</string>
    <string name="alarm_set">Alarm set.</string>
    <string name="settings_were_saved">Your Settings were saved.</string>
    <string name="you_are_clearing">You are about to clear the Debug-Log</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_to_clear">Are you sure you want to clear the Debug-Log?</string>
    <string name="confirm">confirm</string>
    <string name="debug_log_was_cleared">The Debug-Log was cleared.</string>
    <string name="action_canceled">Action canceled</string>
    //Test Menu
    <string name="head_test_menu">Test menu</string>
    <string name="test_button_1">push notification test</string>
    <string name="test_button_2">key generation test</string>
    <string name="test_button_3">risk level test</string>
    <string name="test_button_4">check infection status test</string>
    <string name="test_button_5">log own keys test</string>
    <string name="test_button_6">delete own keys test</string>
    <string name="reset_button_risklevel">reset risk level</string>
    <string name="test_button_7">Transmitting on/off</string>
    <string name="test_button_8">Scanning on/off</string>
    <string name="test_button_9" translatable="false">add Test Contact List</string>
    <string name="test_button_10" translatable="false">Risklevel Algorithm: Calculate Risk level</string>
    <string name="test_button_11" translatable="false">CheckOutDatedInfection</string>
    <string name="test_button_12" translatable="false">SetInfectionAsOutdated</string>
    <string name="test_button_13" translatable="false">Activate 15m business</string>
    <string name="test_button_14" translatable="false">Risklevel Algorithm: Add Indirect Test Contact</string>
    <string name="test_button_15" translatable="false">Risklevel Algorithm: Add Direct Test Contact</string>
    <string name="test_button_16" translatable="false">Risklevel Algorithm: Remove all Test Contacts</string>
    <string name="test_button_17" translatable="false">check ControlKeyExchangeFunction</string>
</resources>